Wade Cranford

www.coderfoundry.com/wadecranford

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5
CSS3
JavaScript/ES6
JQuery
Bootstrap
.NET
C#
MVC
ASP.NET
SQL & Bash
LINQ

Xamarin

WebAPI

CODER FOUNDRY

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

EDUCATION

Snead State Community College, A.S. Computer Science *Boaz, AL · 2010*

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer

Kernersville, NC · July 2020 – September 2020

- · Created three primary projects, including:
 - 1. A portfolio site using C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery.
 - 2. A Financial Portal implemented in three phases. Phase 1: an MVC Web Application, Phase 2: a Web Service that utilizes Swagger and Swashbuckle for integrated testing, Phase 3: A cross platform Xamarin Mobile Application.
 - 3. Fully designed and developed a multi-functional issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security, which also used a Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC5, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables.

CPR: Cell Phone Repair, Service Technician

Charlotte, NC · July 2019 – May 2020

- Responsible for discussing technical issues with customer devices, and explaining possible solutions in an easy to understand manner.
- Performed hardware repairs in a safe and timely manner on customer devices, and maintain a professional and organized station.

Lowe's Home Improvement, Delivery

Auburn, AL & Charlotte, NC · May 2013 – April 2019

- Worked as a pair to deliver lawn equipment and install kitchen appliances to customer homes.
- Communicated with other delivery teams, in-store employees, and customers to organize a convenient delivery experience.